Dick Russell papers, Inclusive: 1924-2011, undated, Bulk: 1964-2003, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- The Man Who Knew Too Much, 1990-2003, undated; 1
  - 1992 Manuscript, 3
    - Book Proposal Package, 1992; 1
      - Chapter 23, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 24, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Chapter 25, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Chapter 26, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 27, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 28, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 29, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 30, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Conclusion, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Timelines, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Appendices (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Appendices (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Corrected Proof, 1992; 2
      - Index, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Photo & Photo Captions, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Introduction, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 1, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Chapter 2, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 3, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Chapter 4, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 5, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Chapter 6, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Chapter 7, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 8, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 9, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 10, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 11, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 12, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 13, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 14, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 16, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 17, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 18, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 19, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Chapter 20, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 21, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Chapter 22, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 23, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Chapter 24, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Chapter 25, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Chapter 26, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Chapter 27, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Chapter 28, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 29, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Chapter 30, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Chapter 33, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Notes and Footnotes, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Original, 1992; 3
      - Front Matter, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Forward by Carl Oglesby, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Preface, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Table of Contents, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Acknowledgements, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Ch. 1: The Man Who Got Himself Arrested, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Ch. 2: First Encounters: El Paso-Los Angeles 1975, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Ch. 3: Cold War, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Ch. 4: Echoes from the Far East, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Ch. 5: Genesis of a Relationship: Nagell and Oswald in Japan, 1957-1958, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Ch. 6: Tokyo Triangles 1958-1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Ch. 7: California Odyssey 1958-1962, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Ch. 8: The CIA, The KGB, and Oswald in the USSR 1959-1962, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Ch. 9: The Mission, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Ch. 10: Nagell’s Soviet Assignments: Oswald’s Return June-December 1962, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Ch. 11: Oswald and the Baron, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Ch. 12: Nagell and the Cuban Exiles: January-April 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Ch. 13: The Attack on General Walker: February-April 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Ch. 14: The Second Plot to Kill JFK, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Ch. 15: Fair Play or Foul? June 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Ch. 16: The Set Up, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Ch. 17: Oswald Recruited: New Orleans August 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Ch. 18: The Third Plot to Kill JFK August 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Ch. 19: Nagell’s Cruel September of 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Ch. 20: CIA vs. KGB: Mysteries of Mexico City, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Ch. 21: Oswald's Strange Voyage: September 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Ch. 22: The Deed, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Ch. 23: Countdown to Dallas: October-November 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Ch. 24: The Right-Wing and the Pentagon, November 1963, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Ch. 25: The Deed: November 22, 1963, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Ch. 26: Patriot Games: The Hunta and the Assassination, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Ch. 27: The Cover Up, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Ch. 28: The Railroading of Richard Case Nagell, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Ch. 29: Nagell’s Disappearance Behind the Iron Curtain 1968-1970, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Ch. 30: Orchestration of the JFK Conspiracy, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Conclusion, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Appendix, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Bibliography, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Corrections, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Notes (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Notes (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Reproduction Request, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Timeline, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 2003 Manuscript, 1999-2003; 4
    - General, 2003; 1
      - Cover, Front Matter, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Introduction, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Forward, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Preface, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Cast of Characters, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Chapter 1: The Man Who Got Himself Arrested, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Chapter 2: First Encounters: El Paso, Los Angeles (1975), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Chapter 3: Cold War: Origins of a Spy (1948-1956), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 4: Echoes from the Far East, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Chapter 5: Genesis of a Relationship: Nagell and Oswald in Japan (1957-1958), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Chapter 6: Tokyo Triangles (1958-1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 7: California Odysseys (1958-1962), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 8: The CIA, the KGB, and Oswald in the USSR (1959-1962), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 9: Double Role in Mexico (Autumn 1962), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 10: Nagell’s Soviet Assignments and Oswald’s Return (June-December 1962), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 11: Oswald and the Baron (1962-1977), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 12: Nagell and the Cuban Exiles (January-April 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 13: The Attack on General Walker (February-April 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 14: The Second Plot to Kill JFK (April-June 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 15: Fair Play or Foul? (June-July 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 16: Oswald First Trip to Mexico City (July-August 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 17: Oswald Recruited: New Orleans (August 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 18: The Third Plot to Kill JFK, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Chapter 19: Nagell’s Cruel September of 1963, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 20: CIA vs. KGB: Mysteries of Mexico City, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Chapter 21: Oswald’s Strange Voyage (September 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 22: The Deed, The Colonel, The Cuban Exiles, and The Mob, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Chapter 23: Countdown to Dallas (October-November 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Chapter 24: The Deed (November 22, 1963), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Chapter 25: Nagell and the Government Cover-Up (November 1963-May 1964), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Chapter 26: The Railroading of Richard Case Nagell (May 1964-April 1968), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Chapter 27: Nagell’s Disappearance Behind the Iron Curtain (1968-1970), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Chapter 28: The Man Who Knew Too Much, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Appendix, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Notes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Bibliography, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Acknowledgements, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Index, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - CIA Updates, 2003; 2
      - Article, “KGB Told Tall Tales About Dallas, Book Says,” James Risen, JFK Lancer News Exchange, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Article, “James Jesus Angleton and the Kennedy Assassination, Part II”, by Lisa Pease, PROBE Magazine, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Marr, Irene, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Text/Notes to be Included, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Article, “The Good Spy”, by Jefferson Morley, Washington Monthly, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Lachy Hulme Edits, 2003; 3
      - Pages 3-120, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - Pages 120-217, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Coalition on Political Assassinations (COPA), 1994-1995, undated; 2
  The Coalition on Political Assassinations series includes financial reports and COPA conference information.
  - General, Year End and Annual Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Abstract “Oswald: Was He Controlled?” by Dick Russell, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, “The Assassination of Martin Luther King Jr., A Summary of the Current State of the Case”, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Packet, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Schedule, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Abstracts, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Agenda, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Open Secrets Newsletter Conference Edition, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Participation Correspondence, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Speakers, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Correspondence, Logistics & Topics, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
- JFK Research, 1977-2002, undated; 3
  The JFK Research series mainly contains materials about the assassination of JFK collected after the publication of The Man Who Knew Too Much in 1992.
  - JFK Library, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - News Clips, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - William Ray Dobkins, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Maurice Bishop, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Mark Zaid/FOIA, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Book Reviews, 1993 November (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Echoes of Conspiracy vol. 15 no. 1, 1993 November 3 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - “The JFK Cover -Up” Newsweek, 1993 November (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - The Third Decade vol. 9 no. 4, 1993 May (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - The Third Decade vol. 9 no. 5, 1993 July (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - The Third Decade vol. 9 no. 6, 1993 September (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - News Clips, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - “Who was Lee Harvey Oswald?” Frontline Rebuttal, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Back Channels vol. 3 no. 3, 1994 September (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Citizens for Truth about the Kennedy Assassination/ PROBE Magazine vol. 1 no. 9, 1994 May (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 1 no. 2, 1994 January (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 1 no. 3, 1994 March (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 1 no. 4, 1994 May (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 1 no. 5, 1994 July (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 1 no. 6, 1994 September (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 1, 1994 November (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Assassination Symposium John F. Kennedy (ASK), 1994 November 18-22 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - “NameBase NewsLine” newsletter no. 4, 1994 January-March (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Open Secrets-Coalition on Political Assassination (COPA) vol. 1 no. 1, 1994 August (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Assassination Chronicles vol. 1 no. 3, 1995 September (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Back Channels vol. 3 no. 4, 1995 May (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Back Channels vol. 4 no. 1, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Catalogue 21- Political Assassinations Conspiracy and the Kennedy Family, 1995 November (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dallas Police Department Evidence Police Report, 1995 August (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 2, 1995 January (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 3, 1995 March (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 4, 1995 May (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 5, 1995 July (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 2 no. 6, 1995 September (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 1, 1995 November (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board Documents Release (1 of 2), 1995 September (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Assassination Records Review Board Documents Release (2 of 2), 1995 September (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - The Key to the Warren Report, American Heritage, 1995 November (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - “Oswald, The CIA Mole Hunt, and OSI,” Peter Dale Scott, 1995 Nov (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - M & A Book Dealer Catalogue, 1995 September (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - “Stone/Nixon”, Newsweek, 1995 December (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Open Secrets-Coalition on Political Assassination (COPA) vol. 1 no. 2, 1995 January (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Posner, Gerald L., 1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Westbrook, W.R., 1995 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Winston Scott, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Assassination Archives & Research Center Quarterly, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 2, 1996 January (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 3, 1996 March (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 4, 1996 May (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 5, 1996 July (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 3 no. 6, 1996 September (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 4 no. 1, 1996 November (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - JFK/Deep Politics Quarterly vol. 1 no. 3, 1996 April (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - JFK/Deep Politics Quarterly vol. 1 no. 4, 1996 July (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - JFK/Deep Politics Quarterly vol. 2 no. 1, 1996 Oct. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - JFK Lancer Resources Catalogue, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - JFK & Vietnam, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Mark Zaid/FOIA, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Open Secrets-Coalition on Political Assassinations (COPA), vol. 1 no. 6/vol. 2 no. 1, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board News Release, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Citizens for Truth about the Kennedy Assassination/PROBE Magazine, 1997 November-December (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - COPA Advisory Board Correspondence, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 4 no. 2, 1997 Jan (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 4 no. 3, 1997 March (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 4 no. 5, 1997 July (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 4 no. 6, 1997 September (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 5 no. 1, 1997 November (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Exner, Judith, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - JFK/Deep Politics Quarterly vol. 2 no. 2, 1997 January (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Political Assassinations Conspiracy and the Kennedy Family, Last Hurrah Bookshop Catalogue 22, 1997 September (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Shaw, Clay L. CIA Historical Review, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Slaton, Claude, 1997 Jun. (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Assassinations Records Review Board, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Citizens for Truth about the Kennedy Assassination (CTKA)/PROBE Magazine, 1998 March — Apr. (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Citizens for Truth about the Kennedy Assassination (CTKA)/PROBE Magazine, November- December 1998 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - COPA-John Judge, 1998 January (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - E-mails, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 5 no. 2, 1998 January (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 5 no. 3, 1998 March (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 5 no. 4, 1998 May (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 6 no. 1, 1998 November (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Russo, Gus, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Mark Julius Gayn/Joseph Kramer Correspondence, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - News Clips, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Telecon Notes, 1998 July-August (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Citizens for Truth about the Kennedy Assassination/PROBE Magazine, 1999 January-February (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 6 no. 2, 1999 January (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - “Mystery of JFK’s Second Brain”, The Consortium, 1999 January (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - “Kennedy-CIA Divergence over Cuba” by Peter Dale Scott, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - The Fourth Decade vol. 8 no. 2, 2001 January (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Mexico and LBJ-Rex Bradford Articles, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - “Now It Can Be Told!” by Allan Witwer, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Subject Files, 1960-2011, undated; 4
  The Subject Files series is arranged alphabetically and contains research topics ranging from Early American History to Watergate. Most subjects deal with scandal, assassinations, or times of turmoil, usually in the context of government or politics.
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), News Clippings, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, Articles, 1972, undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, Federal Bureau of Prisons, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, National Institute of Health, 1972, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, National Prison Project, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Behavior Modification (Mind Control), Prisons, Wisconsin, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - CIA, Abroad, 1974-1977, undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - CIA, Assassination Plots, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - CIA, Assassination Plots, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - CIA, Assassination Plots, 1976-1989 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - CIA, Assassination Plots, undated (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - CIA, Authors & Books, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CIA, Bush Era, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - CIA, Bush Era, 1991 January-June (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CIA, Bush Era, 1991 July-September (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - CIA, Bush Era, 1991 October-November (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - CIA, Chile, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - CIA, Corporate Fronts, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - CIA, Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - CIA, Deaths, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - CIA, Domestic, 1979-1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - CIA, Domestic, 1970-1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - CIA, Editorials, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - CIA, Editorials, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - CIA, “Executive Action”-AMLASH (1 of 2), 1960-1977 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - CIA, “Executive Action”-AMLASH (2 of 2), 1960-1977 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - CIA, House Investigation, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1993 January-June (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1993 July-December (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1994 January-June (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1994 July-December (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1995 January-June (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1995 July-December (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1996 January-June (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1996 July-December (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1997 January-March (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1997 April-June (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1997 July-December (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - CIA, Intelligence, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - CIA, Mail Interrupt, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - CIA, Media, 1976, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - CIA, Missionaries, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - CIA, News Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - CIA, News Clippings, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - CIA, NSA and Eavesdropping, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - CIA, Officials, 1966-1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - CIA, Officials, 1978-1999 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - CIA, Operation Chaos: Domestic Spying and Police Collusion, 1976-1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - CIA, Personnel Changes and Govt. Action, 1978-1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - CIA, Senate Investigation, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - CIA, Society, 1975 March-April (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - CIA, Soviet Union, 1969-1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - CIA, Students and Recruitment, 1967-1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - CIA, Rockefeller Commission, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - CIA, Vietnam Corps, 1970-1975 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Contras, Crack, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Contras, Crack, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Contras, Crack, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Contras, Crack, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Contras, Crack, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Contras, Crack, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Contras, Crack, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Contras, Crack, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Contras, Crack, 1998-1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Contras, Crack, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Contras, Crack, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Contras, Crack, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Contras, Crack, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Contras, Crack, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Contras, Crack, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Contras, Casolaro, Joseph “Danny”, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Cuba, Cuban Embassy Employees (Calderon, Duran), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Cuba, Cuban Exiles, CIA Releases, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Cuba, Cuban Exiles, JFK Library, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Cuba, Cuba Files, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Cuba, Fair Play for Cuba Committee, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Cuba, Nassau Conference, General, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Cuba, Nassau Conference, Interviews, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Cuba, Nassau Conference, Research, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Cuba, Nassau Conference, Sidebar, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Cuba, Highlights, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Cuba, News Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Cuba, Scott, Peter Dale, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cuba, Smith, Wayne, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)